I got news from Hirogato and today I'm going to show you the reptilian PU suits
metallic, sparkly, shiny, silver and I got one in black but what I'm also going to
show you is this crazy one from the Psy UV collection let's go I started with
the black one as you can see and it fits so good so my Hirogato suits are
made to measure that's why the fit is just superior it's really tight so I have to
squeeze a bit into it but I know from experience that the more of them you
wear the suits the easier you get into them because the fabric does stretch a
bit and they get more and more comfortable over time it just looks so
good and I also love the pattern it's subtle but still not just black
Alright, you have the option to customize basically everything.
For the feet we have like I am wearing here socks but you can also get stirrups and you
can also get like no socks or stirrups just a normal leg.
Then for the hands I am wearing the gloves option but there is also the mittens option
and of course also just normal sleeves.
can add a zipper in the crotch area like I did or no zipper. You have the option
to choose a shoulder zip or a back zip like I did and what's also possible are
hoods and I have a hood attached here and there are various options of hoods
to choose from like only the eyes only eyes and nose and face open so you can
check that out. Also check out the webshop I linked in the description text and use
my discount code. Now when I roll up the hood you can see the cat which is the
Hirogato trademark and they have new print technique so it feels a bit sticky
like silicon it is a bit raised so almost 3d. Alright let me change into the
silver one. Okay, silver one and I think it looks really spacey. It gives me kind
of space suit vibes and looks so cool like really really cool metallic. I love it.
I'm going to add some accessories to this one. I decided to crank up the
contrast and go with red. I also got a red bag somewhere over here with silver
details and I'm just because I kind of going to add a metal belt again. Okay so
I think the silver match is really great with the belt and the silver accessories here.
Also the fabric is not 100% smooth, not like PVC. You can also hear that when I
like glide over it and touch it. But it's super stretchy. So when I dressed I first was like,
whew this is tight. But it's stretched enough for me to squeeze into it and it's actually really
comfy. I just love these suits and of course because I added a card stipper it's also really
handy. You can go to the toilet with that for example. The gloves are not the most practical
option here but I just love the full body look with the socks and the gloves. And now we still
have this crazy one here I love it so I'm going to change into that I think
this is such a fun color colors like so psychedelic and it's a side spandex
collection there are several patterns with these colors or different colors
all these kind of psychedelics worry or techie things so check that out and
And it's super comfy because the spandex is really stretchy.
I can't really grab it with the gloves because it's slippery.
So yeah, really stretchy, really comfy.
I opted for one without a crotch zip this time to have a really smooth look.
I do have a back zipper though, of course.
And we get the cute cat.
And the specialty here is that it's UV light reactive.
watching about to try I think it's a completely different pattern and look
now with the UV light I totally dig it and I love that the suit basically has
two personalities and if you're wearing it for partying and stand on the black
light and you have a second look with you alright so let's put up all the
lights and just a UV light and see how that looks. That's so cool!
All right so that was the last suit and now I want you to tell me in the
comments which one was your favorite. I think this one I can't compare it with
first two because it's just so different and for the first two both were equally great i mean black
is black i love black but silver was also top notch so i don't know i can't really decide i
think all of them are great and uh yeah as i said have a look at the hiragato webshop you can see a
lot of suits there customize your dream suit and you can use my discount code for a discount
obviously, and I will see you in the next video. Have a nice day. Bye!
.